<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jürgen Hackl</title>
    <link>https://hackl.science/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jürgen Hackl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hackl.science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>tikz-network</title>
      <link>https://hackl.science/post/2019-10-05-tikznetwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackl.science/post/2019-10-05-tikznetwork/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Check out my tool to visualize complex networks in LaTeX&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>research</title>
      <link>https://hackl.science/post/2019-10-05-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackl.science/post/2019-10-05-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My research interests lie in developing and quantifying a robust understanding of urban resilience with a focus on complex interdependent infrastructure systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pathpy</title>
      <link>https://hackl.science/post/2019-10-05-pathpy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackl.science/post/2019-10-05-pathpy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am the lead developer of pathpy, an OpenSource python package for the analysis of time series data on networks using higher-order and multi-order graphical models.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://hackl.science/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackl.science/about/</guid>
      <description>Short bio Dr Jürgen Hackl is an Assistant Professor at the University of Liverpool and a member of the Data Analytics Group at the University of Zurich. He received his doctorate in Engineering Science from the ETH Zurich in July 2019. His research interests lie in complex urban systems and span both computational modelling and network science. Much of his work has been on improving the understanding, design, and performance of complex interdependent infrastructure systems, affected by natural hazards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://hackl.science/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackl.science/publications/</guid>
      <description>Refereed Journal Publications   Lam, J. C., Hackl, J., Heitzler, M., Adey, B. T., and Hurni, L. (2020). Impact Assessment of Extreme Hydrometeorological Hazard Events on Road Networks Journal of Infrastructure Systems 26(2), 04020005. doi: 10.1061/(ASCE)IS.1943-555X.0000530
  Lam, J. C., Heitzler, M., Hackl, J., Adey, B. T., and Hurni, L. (2020). Modelling the functional capacity losses of networks exposed to hazards. Sustainable and Resilient Infrastructure, 5(1-2), 30&amp;ndash;48. doi: 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://hackl.science/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hackl.science/talks/</guid>
      <description>Hackl, J. (2020). A cloud-based computational platform to manage risk and resilience of buildings and infrastructure systems. 37th International Symposium on Automation and Robotics in Construction (ISARC 2020). Kokura, Japan: IAARC. Conference Date: October 26-30, 2020.
  Hackl, J. (2020). Non-Markovian models for bridge deterioration. 4th International Symposium on Infrastructure Asset Management (SIAM 2020). Chicago, Illinois, USA: Northwestern University. Conference Date: August 20-21, 2020.
  Baumann, J.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>